AM I GOING TO HEAVEN?
NO. THEN AM I GOING TO HELL?
NO!
YOU DIE BEFORE YOUR TIME!
SO WHAT DO I DO?
YOU HAVE 24 HOURS TO DO FOUR GOOD DEEDS.
OR YOU'LL GO TO HELL.
I WAS REBORN IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS FOREST, AND...
OH, HELL.
WHO'S SCREAMING?
PLEASE!
HELP ME!
MY CAT IS STUCK UP IN THAT TREE!
COME HERE, KENNY!
HERE YOU GO!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YOU'RE EVEN BETTER THAN I IMAGINED!
I NEED TO HURRY!
I'VE TRICKED A LOT OF PEOPLE I NEED TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT.
HELP ME!
MY HOUSE IS ON FIRE!
AND MY SON IS STILL INSIDE!
I'LL SAVE YOUR SON, BACON!
YOU'RE NEW SON?
DANG IT!
I CAN ONLY DO GOOD DEEDS!
HERE YOU GO, NOOB!
THANK YOU!
I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME!
NOXLEY!
DO YOU NEED HELP?
THANK GOODNESS SOMEONE CAME!
ACE PUT MY DOG ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE LAVA RIVER!
OH MY GOSH!
I'LL HELP YOU!
JUST CROSS THE RIVER USING THESE BLOCKS!
I'M COMING FOR YOU, ACE!
COME HERE, DOGGY!
THANK YOU, VERITY!
I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME, AND I STILL NEED ONE MORE GOOD DEED!
I HAVE TO FIND SOMETHING GOOD TO DO!
WELCOME BACK!
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU WERE ONE GOOD DEED!
SORT OF GETTING INTO HEAVEN!
CAN YOU GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE?
PLEASE!
I'LL GIVE YOU THIS SWORD WITH AMAZING POWERS!
DOES HE DESERVE ANOTHER CHANCE?
THANKS SO!
LEAVE A LIKE!